Yeah, l've learned something today.
You and l, in so many ways...
(Sheldon:)...other than intelligence
and what counts, we're the same.
(Mrs Cooper:)Sweetheart, are you sick?
(Sheldon:)I hope so, because if this is well,
Iife isn't worth living.
Sugar pie, you are burning up.
We've got to get you to bed.
- Okay.
- Don't worry.
(Mrs Cooper:)Mama's here to take care of her baby.
(Sheldon:)And just to be clear, only her baby
and not these other people.
(Sheldon:)Of course.
(Sheldon:)Can I have tea with honey
and toast with the crust cut off?
- You can have whatever you want.
- Brr. Thanks, Mom. You're the best.
(Mrs Cooper:)Boy, last time I put VapoRub on you,
you didn't have hair on your chest.
(Sheldon:)I know, it filled in last year.